McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus, 1871-1907 (bulk 1895-1905): Finding Aid TC040
Manuscripts Division
- Series 3: Miscellaneous Materials, 1683-1988 December 19; 44 boxes; 9 folders; 6 items
  - George L. Fox Pantomimes purchased by Barnum and Bailey, 1892; 2 boxes; 9 folders; 2 items
    - "Humpty Dumpty" (program), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 64, Volume V3, Page p. 162-163)
    - "Humpty Dumpty" (program containing sketch of G.L. Fox's life"), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 64, Volume V3, Page p. 164)
    - "Humpty Dumpty" Abroad (large handbill), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 64, Volume V3, Page p. 165-166)
    - "House that Jack Built" (large handbill), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 64, Volume V3, Page p. 167)
    - "Humpty Dumpty" (program), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 64, Volume V3, Page p. 168)
    - "Humpty Dumpty" (handbill), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 64, Volume V3, Page p. 169)
    - Pages from Bow Bell's Christmas Annual, "Tales of Golden Goose" (partial), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 64, Volume V3, Page p. 170)
    - Program from "Golden Egg", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 64, Volume V3, Page p. 171)
    - News clippings on Fox's performances, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 64, Volume V3, Page p. 174-176)
    - Loose clipping, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 64, Volume V3, Page p. 177)
    - Prop list for "Schoolmaster", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Prop lists for "Golden Axe", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Prop lists for "Dame Trot and Her Comical Cat", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Prop lists for "Magie Pills", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Prop lists for "Jack and the Beanstalk", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Prop list for "Pongo", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Prop lists for "Red Game", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Prop lists for "Dame Trot and Her Comical Cat", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Prop list for "Raoul", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Prop list for "Jacko!", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Prologue and prop list for "Fair Lovers", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Prop list for "Mystic Cave", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Prop list for "Jack and Gill", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Prop list for "Soldier for Love", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Prop list for "Asphodel, or the Magpie Pen", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Prop list for "Dechalumeah", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Prop list for "Little Boy Blue", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Prop list for unidentified pantomime, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Prop list for "Magie Barrel", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Prop list for "Frisky Cobbler", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Prop list for "Humpty Dumpty", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Partial prop list for unidentified pantomime, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - series of 23 short pantomimes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder Book 24)
    - Three property plot books for unidentified pantomimes, dates not examined; 3 folders (Box 65, Folder Books 25-27)
    - Property plot book for "Humpty Dumpty", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder Book 28)
    - Partial description of action of pantomime, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder Book 29)
    - Misc. scripts, verse, lists, some unidentified, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder Bundle 30)
    - "Little Boy Blue" scripts, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder Bundle 31)
    - "Three Blind Mice" scripts, description, and song sheet, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder Bundle 32)
    - "Humpty Dumpty" scripts, descriptions, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder Bundle 33)
    - "Jack and Gill" scripts and description of action, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder Bundle 34)
    - Witches and Mephistopheles skit, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - "Jack and the Beanstalk" prop list, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - Maps, dates not examined; 1 box
    - "Londres via Ostende" map of Europe, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 1)
      (including England, Austria, Holland)
    - (1) folded map of Holland with box, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - (2) folded maps of Switzerland, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - (2) folded maps of Belgium, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - (3) maps of Germany, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - (1) folded map of Austria, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - (6) maps of France, dates not examined; 5 folders (Box 66, Folder 7-11)
  - Railway Maps, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Official railway map of England and Wales, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Official railway map of Scotland, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Official railway map of England and Wales, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper map of the United Kingdom, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Non-McCaddon Couriers and Programs, 1870-1956 May 26; 1 box
    - Barnum and Bailey, Lalla Rookh, The Departure from Delhi (Crookston, ), Wednesday July 7; no year; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Wizard Prince of Arabia, 1914; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Columbus and the Discovery of America, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Greatest Show on Earth, Madison Square Garden, 1897 April 9; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Same as above, April 9-11, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Fall of Babylon, 1890; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Buffalo Bill, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Border Lights, 1886, Madison Square Garden, 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Robbins Bros. Circus, 1938; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Dan-Rice Circus, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - 1917 Courier, 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Forepaugh and Sells Bros. 1900 April 4-7, Madison Square Garden, 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Forepaugh Couriers, 1870; 1876; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - La Mont Bros., Erie, PA, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Walter L. Main Circus, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Special Herald (one day preceding circus), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Courier, Erie, PA, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - John Robinson's Circus. 1930 September 12, Russelville, 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Ringling Bros, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Joan of Arc, 1912; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Courier, 1917, Dallas, 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Solomon and the Queen of Sheba, 1915; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Ringling Bros., Barnum and Bailey, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Magazine of Wonders, 1938; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Spaulding and Rogers, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - 1956 May 26, Advance Bill, 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Christmas Cards from people involved in the Circus to "Flanners 3 Ring Circus", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 11)
      Includes a photo "Seasons Greetings" by Pat Valdo; John Ringling is pictured on the left.
    - Material relating to exhibitions on the circus, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Handbills, dates not examined; 2 boxes
    Consists of approximately 190 letterheads, programs, and advertisements, dating from approximately 1909-1938, from the following circuses:
    - Tom Atkinson, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - A.G. Backes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Al. G. Barnes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Barnet Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Bentley's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Barney's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Boy Scouts Indoor Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Campbell Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Castle's Congress of Animal Actors, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Christy Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Carl Clark, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - M.L. Clark and Sons, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Cole and Rogers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Cole Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Cooper Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Dakota Max Ranch Wild West, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Davison Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - DeRue Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Downie Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - E.E. Coleman's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Eldridge and Benton, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Elks Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - J.H. Eschman, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Franko Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Gentry Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Great American Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Great Barrett, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Great Walter's Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Mighty Haag's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Hagenbeck Wallace, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Harris Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Hope Fire Co., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Hunts, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - L.W. Hoffman Jr., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Jethro Almond, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Jones Bros. and Wilsons, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - William H. Kasiska, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Rose Kilian, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - LaMont Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Lee Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Lewis Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Lockery Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Walter L. Main, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - McCall Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 69)
    - Mighty Haag's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Mighty Watson, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Odd Fellow's Carnival, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Dan Rice, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Pennsylvania Excursion, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Dan Pilmore's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Polack Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Rentz Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Rhoda Royal, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Rice Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Richards Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Robbins Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Robinson's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Roger's Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - John Robinson's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Robinson Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Sells Floto, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Silvan-Drew, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Sparks, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Stone and Murray's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Sun Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Eddy Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Snyder Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Tompkins, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - King and Goldman, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Wallace Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Welch's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Wesley Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Wheeler and Santelle's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Wheeler and Almond, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Al. F. Wheeler, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Wheeler Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - La Tena's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Weidemann Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Wintermute Bros. and Hall's, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - World Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
    - Yankee Robinson, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 70)
  - Small Circus Pictures & Film (purchased sets), 1909-1948; 1 box
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1930; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1948; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1947; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1947; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1948; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1938; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, Winter Quarters, 1946; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1946; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1946; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1946; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1946; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1946; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1944; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, preview performance, Sarasota, Florida, 1944; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1944; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1943; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1943; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1943; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1939; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1939; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, 1909; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, Circus Films, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Milwaukee Circus Parade, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Wagon and Costume Designs, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Wagon design for "Nursery Rhymes", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Costume designs for "Nursery Rhymes" tableau, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Wagon design for "Babes in the Wood", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Costume design for "Cinderella or the Glass Slipper", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Wagon design for "The Queen of Hearts", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Wagon design for "Jack and the Beanstalk", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Costume designs for "Jack and the Beanstalk", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Wagon design for "Sleeping Beauty", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Costume designs for "Babes in the Wood" tableau, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Wagon design for "Blue Beard", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Costume designs for "Toys", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Wagon design for "Toys", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Wagon design for "Aladdin", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Costume designs for May Pole Dancers, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Wagon design for "Toys and Games", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Oversize Matted Watercolors, 1683-1789; 1 box
    - William Penn's Treaty with the Indians, 1683; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Captain Smith's Rescue by Pocahantas, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Signing the Declaration of Independence, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Washington's Inauguration, 1789; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Untitled Watercolor, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Oversize Materials, 1893-1938; 1 box
    - Miller Bros. 101 Ranch, Real Wild West Show, program, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Christmas card from Radio Department, Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Christmas card from Outdoor Ad Department, Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Souvenir of S. Sarasota County, special Circus Edition of The Gondolier, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Photo: Center poles on wagon on railroad car, 1935; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Ringling-Barnum Troupe, 1933; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Grounds, Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, Scranton, Pa, 1938; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Inside Big Top with elephants, Ringling Bros. Barnum and Bailey, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Hagenbeck Wallace Troupe, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Walter L. Main Circus Troupe, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Miller Bros. 101 Ranch, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Sells-Floto Clowns, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Singer's Circus, Side Show Entrance, 1931; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Tom Mix Circus Troupe, 1937; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Stars and Celebrities of Christy Bros. Circus, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Cole Bros. "America" Wagon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Cole Bros., Clyde Beatty Circus, 1937; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - George Washington Bi-Centennial Spectacular, Downie Bros. Circus, 1932; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Downie Bros. Circus, 1937; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Barnum and Bailey Courier, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Barnum and Bailey Advance Courier, 1917; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Barnum and Bailey 1893 Courier, 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Courier, P.T. Barnum's Greatest Show on Earth and Great London Circus, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Blueprint of Big Top Set Up, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - 1896 Parade Sketches, 6 boxes
    - Germany: Cuirassier, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Russia: Czar Alex II, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Russia: Cossack, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Russia: Chevalier Guarde, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Sweden: King Oseau, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Turkey: Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Turkey: The Sultan, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Turkey: Lances-Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Turkey: Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Painting: "Dieu et Mon Droit", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Siam: Banner Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Italy: Cavalry (Genoa Regiment), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Italy: Safe Guard-Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Italy: King Humbert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Japan: Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Persia: Escort to the Shah, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Persia: The Shah, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Persia: Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Holland: Hussar, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Siam: Escort, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Belgium: King Leopold II, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - France: President Carnot, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Sweden: Dragoon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Germany: Uhlan-Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Siam: King Theeban (?), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Egypt: Arabs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Browning, King, & Company-Uniform & Contracting Deparment: List of Costumes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - United States of America: U.S. Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Russia: Chevalier Garde-Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Egypt: The Khedive, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - England: Hussar (11th), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - England: Groom & Postillion (?), Royal State Livery, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Russia: Czar Alex II, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Browning, King, & Company-Uniform & Contracting Department: List of Costumes, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - France: Hussar, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Spain: Gendarme, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - United States of America: "Uncle Sam", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Russia: Cossack (Ural), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Germany: Emperor William II, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - United States of America-"Columbia": Cavalry, Heavy Artillery, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Japan: Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Egypt: Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - China: Cavalry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Germany: Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Italy: Cavalry (Genoa Regiment), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Austria: Hungarian Life Guard-Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Belgium: Guide-Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Belgium: King Leopold II, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Sweden: Dragoon (?), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Austria: Emperor Francis Joseph, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Belgium: Lancer (?), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Egypt: Cavlary, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Belgium: Guide, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Spain: King's Escort, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Sweden: Horse Guards, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Italy: King Humbert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Itlay: Life Guard-Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Spain: King's Escort, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Germany: Cuirassier, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - England: Hussar (11th)-Standard Bearer, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - England: Royal Guard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 6)